-1868 England-
(ﾀﾞﾘｵ)ウヘヘヘヘ｡
おい見ろよ 事故だぜ！
Oy, look at this! There's been an accident!
(ﾀﾞﾘｵ)おェッ！ ひぇ～｡
Bloody hell, looks like he died right away...
(ﾀﾞﾘｵ)ひでえ｡
こっちのやつも 即死だな｡➡
ぬかるみに 足を取られて
こんな崖下まで 落下したのか｡➡
Horse must'a slipped on the rocks and the whole lot tumbled down here.
These nobles are quite the picture of wealth, wouldn't you say?
にしても さすがは貴族｡
いい身なりしていやがる｡
(女性)旦那！
馬車の中 女は死んでるけど➡
Dario!
The woman in there is dead, but the baby's still alive!
赤ん坊の方は 生きてるよ｡
子供をかばったんだね この人｡
She must have sacrificed herself to save it...
(ﾀﾞﾘｵ)赤ん坊!?
そんなの ほっときやがれ！
I don't give a rat's arse about some baby!
(女性)な… 何すんのさ!?
W-What are you doing?!
Ain't it obvious, you bint!?
(ﾀﾞﾘｵ)決まってんだろ！ まぬけ！
We're relievin' em of their valuables!
金目の物を頂く！
ん？ 何だ？ これは｡
What have we here?
(ﾀﾞﾘｵ)き… 気味の悪い仮面だ｡
こいつは 要らねえな｡
Some bizarre lookin' mask...
It ain't worth keeping.
Give me a hand here!
おい 手伝え！ 前歯 引っこ抜いて
歯医者に持ってくぞ！
Grab his teeth, we can sell em' to a dentist!
Fetch a fair price, they will!
高く 売れんだ！
おげェ!?
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)き… 君…｡
Y-you there... did... did you save me?
君が介抱してくれたのか？
ありがとう…｡
Thank you...
妻は？
妻と息子は？ ２人は無事か？
My wife...
My wife and my son... were you able to rescue them?
くたば… いや ご夫人と御者は
既に亡くなっておりました｡
The bitch... err, I mean... the lady seems to have passed away, unfortunately.
で… でも 赤ちゃんは 無事です｡
The kid seems all right, though.
これも 運命か｡
Perhaps this is fate at work...
I am from the house of Joestar...
私の名は ジョースター｡
命を救ってくれた 礼をしたい｡
I would like to repay you for saving my life.
また 気を失う前に
あなたの名を 聞かせてほしい｡
Please, before I lose consciousness again, please tell me your name.
(ﾀﾞﾘｵ)《ああっ！ こいつ 俺を
命の恩人と思ってるようだな｡➡
This damned fool thinks I'm the one that saved his life!
Bloody idiot! Let's see how far I can play this fool...
この バカめ！ ケケケ！➡
名乗って 損はなかろう》
The name is Dario Brando, my good man.
ダリオ･ブランドーといいやす｡
Mister Brando...
ミスター･ブランドー｡
この ジョースター
決して 恩は忘れはしまい｡
The Joestars... always stand by their word.
-12 Years Later-
≪(ﾀﾞﾆｰの鳴き声)
(ｼﾞｮﾅｻﾝ)よ～し いい子だ！
That's a good boy!
父さん いってきます！
Father, I'm off!
Be careful, Jojo!
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)
気を付けるんだぞ！ ジョジョ｡
行くよ ダニー！
(ﾀﾞﾆｰの鳴き声)
Let's go, Danny!
Some-Stuffs Presents
(ﾀﾞﾘｵのせきこみ)
Dio!
(ﾀﾞﾘｵ)ディオ ここへ来い｡
ゴホッ ゴホッ！
Please, come here...
Dio, can you hear me?!
(ﾀﾞﾘｵ)ディオ 聞こえねえのか!?
(ﾃﾞｨｵ)ふぅ…｡
何だい 父さん｡ 薬かい？
What now, father? More medicine?
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
(ﾀﾞﾘｵ)バッキャロー！➡
I don't need no bleedin' elixirs, you little git!
んな 効きもしねえ薬
要らねえんだよ！➡
Get me booze! If you can afford medicine, then you can afford liquor!
酒だ！ 薬 買う金あったら
酒 買ってこい！
はぁ… ジョジョ！ マナー！
Jojo... mind your manners.
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい｡
Check.
チェック｡
(男性)うっ！
くっ… ほらよ｡
Here, take it...
Timing:
Fadeout4
How's your dinner, you little brat?!
いいざまだな！ くそがき！
ぐっ…｡
Quality Check:
Tonitonichopchop
(ｴﾘﾅ)やめて！
返して！ 返して！
Stop it!
Give it back! Give it back!
Oy, Erina!
(少年１)おい エリナ！
この人形 買ってもらったのか？
Who bought you this doll?
That rich father of yours? That old quack...
(少年１)
お前のおやじ やぶ医者のくせに
もうけてっからな！
Now...
どら… よし！
人形の服を 脱がせてやるぜ！
Why don't we take a look underneath that dress?
あそこが
本物と同じかどうか 見てやる｡
Let's see if those naughty parts look like the real thing!
Visual Typesetting:
Fadeout4
(少年たち)
ハハハ！ 泣いた～！
She's crying!
エリナ！ エリナ！
泣き虫エリナ！ ヘッヘッヘ！
Erina! Erina!
Erina the crybaby!
やめろ！
人形を返してやるんだ！
Stop that!
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Give her the doll back!
(少年２)何だ？ お前！
(少年１)エリナの知り合いか!?
Who the hell are you?! One of Erina's friends?
Just because I don't know her doesn't mean I won't come to her aid!
知らない子だが
僕には 戦う理由がある！
You... little... punk!
この野郎…｡
この～！
女の子の前だからって！
Quit trying to show off!
ギャッ… うう～｡
Well look at what we have here: a little pansy!
(少年２)何でえ｡
こいつ てんで弱いぞ！
ギャハハハハハ！
I don't think I've ever seen anything so sad!
これ以上 惨めなことがあろうか！
助けに入って
逆に やられてやがる｡
He comes runnin' in to save her, but takes a beating instead!
うう…｡
(少年１)あっ！ こいつ➡
Come on now, he's the only son of the Joestar family!
ジョースター家の一人息子だ！
I've got nothin' personal against the rich, I just hate them!
俺は 金持ちに恨みはねえが
とにかく 嫌いだ！➡
Now I'm really gonna let you have it!
お高くとまるんじゃあ
ねえぜ！ 思い知れ！
And some of this!
Dio... I ain't got much longer...
ディオ
俺は もう 長いことはねえ｡
分かるんだ…｡ ゴホッ！
You understand, right?
When I die, take this letter and go to the address written here...
俺が死んだら
この手紙を出して 宛名の所へ｡
Go and stay with the Joestars!
ジョースター家へ行け｡
こいつは 俺に恩があるんだ｡
That old fool owes me...
And you're a sharp lad...You ought to be a rich and powerful man... who won't take no from anyone...
お前は 頭がいい｡
誰にも負けねえ
一番の金持ちになれよ！
うわっ！
金持ちは てめえの敷地内だけで
遊びやがれ！
If you're so bloody rich, then go play in your mansion's yard!
Let's get goin'.
(少年２)行こうぜ！
うっ… ああ…｡
Are you...?
(ｴﾘﾅ)あ… あの…｡
いいから ほっといて！
I'm fine! Leave me alone!
Please, leave me be! I didn't do this to endear myself to you!
向こうへ行けよ！
僕は 君に感謝されたくって➡
あいつらに 向かって
行ったんじゃあないぞ！
I only did this because I made a vow to be a true gentleman!
僕は 本当の紳士を
目指しているからだ！
I did it because you were a lady in need of assistance!
君が 女の子で
困っていたからだ｡
Even if your opponent is bigger, and you're sure that he can not be beaten...
相手が 大きいやつだからって
負けると 分かっているからって➡
In spite of these things, a gentleman will always stand up for what is right!
紳士は 勇気を持って戦わなくては
ならないときが あるからだぞ！
《でも いつか
勝てるようになってやる！》
One of these days, I'll be strong enough to win...
You were a disgusting, petty man...
《醜くって ずる賢くって➡
You put my mother through hell, at the cost of her life...
You were the worst father imaginable.
母に苦労かけて 死なせ
最低の父親だったぜ！➡
一番の金持ちになれだと？
ああ なってやるとも｡➡
You say I could become the richest man around?
You're damn right I will.
利用できるものは
何でも 利用してやる！➡
I'll make use of anyone, and anything I can get my hands on.
That goes for this so-called noble Joestar as well...
この
ジョースターとかいう 貴族も》
You scrap of garbage!
クズめ！
And I will not be denied, not by anyone...
《誰にも負けない男になる！》
ジョナサン･ジョースター｡
Jonathan Joestar...
(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)〈この物語は
謎の石仮面にまつわる➡
This is the story of two young men, their fates intertwined by a mysterious stone mask... and the adventure that followed.
２人の少年の 数奇な運命を追う
冒険譚である〉
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
#some-stuffs@irc.rizon.net
Episode 1: "Dio the Intruder."
≪(馬車の音)
あっ…｡
(馬の鳴き声)
誰だろう？ あっ！
Who could he be?
Oh, you must be Dio Brando!
君は ディオ･ブランドーだね？
And you're Jonathan Joestar...
そういう君は
ジョナサン･ジョースター｡
みんな
｢ジョジョ｣って呼んでるよ｡
Everyone calls me Jojo. It's nice to meet you.
これから よろしく｡
≪(ﾀﾞﾆｰの鳴き声)
Danny!
ダニー！
Let me introduce you, this is Danny. He's my beloved pet...
紹介するよ ダニーってんだ｡
僕の愛犬でね｡
心配ないよ｡
決して 人は かまないから｡
Don't worry, he'd never bite anyone.
《ふん！》
Wh-why did you do that?!
な… 何をするんだ！ 許さん！
I'll never forgive you!
《こいつが
ジョースター家の跡継ぎか》
This is the heir to the Joestar family...
《家も 金も 人も 全て持った
坊ちゃん面だな｡➡
He's had his whole privileged life handed to him on a silver platter.
I'll push his mind to the breaking point, and eventually I, Dio, shall be...
精神的に追い詰め
ゆくゆくは この ディオが！》
≪(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)どうしたんだね？
What happened?
What's going on here?
一体 何事かね？
My apologies, sir. The dog came at me so suddenly. I was startled...
すみません｡
急に 犬が飛びかかってきたので➡
とっさに…｡
えっ!?
《ふん！》
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)ようこそ ディオ君｡
今から 君は 私たちの家族だ｡
Welcome, Dio, my boy!
As of today, you're part of the family.
諸君 この ディオ･ブランドー君は
私の命の恩人の ご子息だ｡
All of you, this is Dio Brando, the son of the man who saved my life.
ジョジョと
同等に扱うよう 頼むよ｡
As of today, I want you to treat him the same way you do Jojo.
Very well, sir.
(執事)かしこまりました｡
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)ディオ君も 遠慮なく➡
As for you, Dio... I hope you can enjoy the same lifestyle that Jojo has.
ジョジョと同じように
生活してくれたまえ｡
ジョースター卿
ご厚意 大変 感謝いたします｡
Lord Joestar, you have my deepest gratitude for your kindness.
ジョジョも 母親を亡くしている｡
Jojo lost his mother as well... and you're both the same age.
それに 同い年だ｡
仲良くしてやってくれたまえ｡
I hope you get along.
ジョジョ
ダニーのことは もういいね？
Jojo, the matter with Danny has been settled, I hope?
はい｡ 僕も 急に
知らない犬が 走ってきたら➡
Yes, sir...
I suppose I'd be startled too, if a dog I didn't recognize came running at me...
びっくりすると思うし
気にしてません｡
I won't let it bother me.
I do wish he'd apologize...
《本当は
ひと言 謝ってほしいな｡➡
でも これから
一緒に暮らすんだし➡
But if we're going to be living together, I want to be friends as soon as possible.
早く 友達にならなくちゃ》
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)来たまえ ディオ君｡
君の部屋に案内しよう｡
Come along, Dio. I'll show you to your room.
はい｡ あっ…｡
Yes, sir.
ん？
うぁぁ！ う… う！
何してんだ？
What do you think you're doing? Keep your filthy hands off my luggage!
気安く 僕のかばんに
触るんじゃあないぜ！
え？
この 小汚い手で➡
I'm telling you not to soil them with your grubby fingers, you buffoon!
触るなと言ったんだ！
まぬけが！
I was going to carry them for-
運んであげようと…｡
結構！
That will be quite all right!
くげッ！ ぐぐぐ…｡
早速 召し使いに 運んでもらう｡
Let's have the servants carry them.
Listen here, Jojo...
いいか ジョジョ｡ 君の家に
やっかいになるからといって➡
Don't you dare get high and mighty with me,
because I'm living under the same roof as you now.
僕に威張ったりするなよな｡
僕は 一番が好きだ｡
ナンバーワンだ！
I adore being the best, being number one!
And I won't let anyone try to lord over me...
誰だろうと
僕の前で 威張らせはしない！
What?! I just want to be friends...
そんな… 僕は 仲良くしようと｡
もう１つ｡ 僕は 犬が嫌いだ｡
And one more thing: I hate dogs.
怖いんじゃあない｡
人間に へいこらする態度に➡
I'm not afraid of them. But their subservient attitude towards humans disgusts me.
虫ずが走るのだ！
So keep that simple-minded Danny far away from me.
あの ダニーとかいうアホ犬を
僕に近づけるなよな｡
What are you two doing? Hurry along now!
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)
２人とも 何をしておるのだ？
早く 来なさい｡
Yes, sir!
はい｡
With Dio's sudden arrival, Jojo's once
carefree life has become filled with grief...
〈ディオの登場により
楽しかった ジョジョの生活は➡
とても つらいものとなっていく〉
ギャッ‼
また 間違えたぞ ジョジョ！
You made another mistake, Jojo!
Look at Dio! Twenty correct answers out of twenty questions!
ディオを見ろ！
20問中 20問正解だ！
あっ！
Jojo! And you claim to be a gentleman?! Your etiquette is atrocious!
ジョジョ！
お前 それでも 紳士か！
作法がなっとらんぞ！ 作法が！
もう
ジョジョの食器を下げたまえ｡
Take Jojo's food away.
えっ!?
今晩は 食事抜きだ！
There will be no dinner for you tonight!
Seeing Dio has made me realize how much I have spoiled you!
ディオが来てから お前を
甘やかしていたのを 悟った！
As a father, I am ashamed!
親として 恥ずかしい！
ディオの作法は 完璧だぞ！
Dio's etiquette is perfect!
ふん！ まぬけが｡
Buffoon...
And the next contender is... Jonathan Joestar!
(司会)続いて 紹介するは
ジョナサン･ジョースター！➡
彼は 最近 力をつけてきました｡
He's been showing some real muscle lately!
(司会)そして 対戦相手ですが
実は ここで 変更があります｡
And for his opponent... well, actually, there's been a change to the fight card...
えっ？
(司会)まだ 名前しか知らない➡
We only know his name, but this young man just arrived in town...
この町に来たばかりの 友人です｡
《ま… まさか！》
I-It can't be...
Allow me to introduce...
(司会)紹介します｡
ディオ･ブランドー君です｡
Dio Brando!
Listen up! The first one to land a clean blow to the face wins the match!
いいかい？ 顔面に
一発でも食らえば その場で負け｡
では！
(ｺﾞﾝｸﾞ)
Let's begin!
Get him, Jojo!
(観客１)いけ～ ジョジョ！
Show the newcomer what you're made of!
(観客２)
そんな よそ者 やっちまえ！
おッ！ うぁ！
(観客３)何だ？ あの動きは!?
(観客１)見たこともない動きだ｡
How's he doing that?!
I've never seen anyone move like that before!
《あ… 当たらない》
I can't hit him!
Jojo... you're a lot better at throwing a punch than I expected.
《ジョジョ こいつ 思ったより
鋭いパンチだ｡➡
But that doesn't matter!
だがね！》
うごっ！ オゲェ｡
《見せてやるぞ｡
ごろつきどもがやる➡
Let me give you a little taste of the cutthroat world of back-alley boxing!
貧民街
ブースボクシングの技巧をな！➡
Take this!
味わいな！》
There it is!
(司会)入った～！
ジョジョの負けだ‼
Jojo loses!
《まだまだ 安心するなよ｡
ジョジョ！➡
I'm not through with you yet, Jojo!
このまま 親指を
こいつの目の中に 突っ込んで➡
I'll drive my thumb right through your eye...
And put you down for good!
殴り抜ける！》
(歓声)
(観客２)すごい！ すごいやつだ！
(観客３)ディオ～！
Amazing! He's really something!
Dio!
(観客４)ディオ！
君 すごいじゃないか！
Dio! That was really impressive!
(観客１)
今のは どうやったんだい？
How'd you get to be so good?!
新しいボクシングの
防御テクニックを使っただけさ｡
It was just some modern parrying methods that are used in the city.
特別 ここにいる者だけに
教えてやってもいい｡
I wouldn't mind showing you chaps some moves.
本当かい？
Really?!
But I wouldn't tell Jojo if I were you.
でも ジョジョには
絶対 教えるなよ｡
あいつは すぐ
秘密を漏らすやつだからな｡
He's got a big mouth, after all.
(観客３)え？ そうなのか｡
(観客２)知らなかったよ｡
Really...
I had no idea!
Why... That was deliberate... why would he do that?!
なぜ！ わざとだ！
なぜ こんなことを！
《フフフ｡ 孤独は
人間を空っぽにするからな｡➡
Solitude can sap a man of his will to live...
And I won't stop until Jojo's an empty shell.
ジョジョを
無気力な ふぬけにしてやる｡➡
そして 次第に やつから
全てのものを取り上げ➡
I will take everything that he loves, one by one.
大人になるころには その全てを
俺のものにしてやる！》
In the end. it will all be mine!
Dio, that scoundrel...
くそっ！ ディオめ｡
惨めだ｡
どんどん 侵略される気分だ｡
It's pathetic. I feel like he's taking over my entire life...
Come on, let's hurry up!
≪(少年１)おい 急ごうぜ｡
ん？
お～い どこ 行くんだい？
Hey, where are you guys going? Come on up here!
こっち来なよ｡ 一緒に遊ぼうぜ！
(少年たち)ん？
Hey, did you boys hear something?
(少年１)
おい 変なのが 何か言ってるぜ｡
Ignore him. He'll just tattle on us.
(少年２)
無視 無視｡ チクられるからな｡
What did you say?!
何だって!?
待て！ 誰が チクリだって!?
Who are you calling a tattletale?!
Let's go.
(少年３)行こうぜ｡
(少年１)チクリ魔 ジョジョめ！
Jojo the tattletale! Hang around him and he'll tell people everything!
こいつと遊ぶと
何でも 他人に話されるぜ｡
(少年３)バッキャロー！
待てよ 戻ってこい！
Wait a moment! Get back here!
When did I ever tattle on anyone?!
僕が いつ 何を
告げ口したってんだよ～！
Jojo the tattletale!
(少年たち)チクリ魔 ジョジョ！
ギャハハハハ！
ディオ！ ディオだな｡
Dio! Dio's doing this to me!
彼らに 僕の不利な でたらめを
吹き込んだんだ｡
He's spreading lies about me!
なぜか ディオは 僕を
陥れることばかりしている！
Everything he does seems to be deliberately against me!
くそっ！ ディオ！
Dio, you bastard!
Dio!
ディオ！ ディオ！
ディオ！ ディオ～！
Dio! Dio!
Dio!
ぐわ～！
《彼が 家に来てから
僕の生活は めちゃめちゃ｡➡
My life is a mess now.
Ever since he came to live at the house... I'm all alone, now!
孤独だ！》
(ﾀﾞﾆｰの鳴き声)
ダニー お前だけは ディオが
何したって 僕の友達だよね｡
Danny... at least I'll always have a friend in you, no matter what Dio does...
(ﾀﾞﾆｰの鳴き声)
(枝が折れる音)
ん？
Who was that girl just now?
誰だ？ 今の女の子｡
I think I've seen her somewhere before...
どこかで 会ったことあるような
気もするけど｡
あっ！ 僕のハンカチ！
My handkerchief!
I see! Thank you for the grapes!
そうか！
ぶどう ありがとう！
ねえ！ あしたも ここにいるから
君も おいでよ！
I'll be here tomorrow, so come by again!
ヘヘヘ｡
Leaving without saying a word...
黙って
たったのひと言も 言わないで｡
What a cute girl...
女の子って カワイイな｡
Love!
〈恋！ その すてきな好奇心が
ジョジョを行動させた〉
Jojo was overwhelmed by that tender emotion.
The two of them quickly became friends, and
Jojo soon found her foremost in his thoughts.
〈２人は たちまち 友達になり
ジョジョは 彼女に夢中になった〉
Erina... Erina Pendleton.
《エリナ…
エリナ･ペンドルトン｡➡
なんて かわいらしいんだろう》
She's absolutely dazzling!
ジョジョ 何を彫ってるの？
Jojo, what are you doing?
Oh Jojo, you wicked boy!
まあ！
ジョジョったら いけない人！
I'm not with this ruffian!
知らない！
じゃあね！ バイバーイ！
See you later! Bye bye!
ふん！
あっ…｡
Hey there... you're Erina, right?
やあ！
君 エリナって名なのかい？
You certainly seem to be close friends with Jojo...
ジョジョと
随分 仲が良さそうだね｡
I thought it was strange...
おかしいと思ったんだ｡
He should have been tormented, after all...
落ち込んでるはずの あいつが
最近 浮かれてると思ったら➡
But this certainly explains his good mood.
こういうわけだったのか｡
H-he did it!
や… やった！
(ｴﾘﾅ)うぐっ！
That's Dio for you! He does things that normal men wouldn't dare to!
さすが ディオ！
俺たちに できないことを➡
平然と やってのける！
そこに しびれる！ 憧れるゥ！
That's what makes him so electrifying! It's incredible!
君 もう
ジョジョと キスはしたのかい？
Have you kissed Jojo yet?
Probably not...
まだだよなあ｡
初めての相手は
ジョジョではない！
And now your first kiss wasn't with Jojo...
この ディオだ！
It was with me, Dio!
《手段は 問題ではない｡➡
The reason doesn't matter... only the fact that she kissed me!
キスをしたという
結果があればいい｡➡
Now her relationship with Jojo will be over...
これで ジョジョとの仲も
終わりになる｡➡
ジョジョには 決して
友人も 恋人も与えん！》
I won't let Jojo have friends or lovers!
L-Look! That girl... she's...
あっ！ み… 見ろ｡
こ… こいつ 一体!?
She's washing her mouth with the water from that dirty puddle!
(少年１)
こいつ 一体 何 考えてんだ!?
(少年２)
泥水で 口を洗っているぞ！
Is she mad?! There's a river right over there!
頭 おかしいんじゃねえか？
近くに 川もあるのによ｡
こ… この女！
You... You foul bitch!
You'd dare rinse your mouth out with muddy water just to defy me?!
わざと 泥で洗って
自分の意思を示すか！
ううっ！
Damn her! How could I let a mere woman rattle me like that...
《くそっ！
この ディオともあろう者が➡
たかが 女ごときに…》
もういい！ 行こう｡
Enough!
Let's go...
あっ… お～い エリナ～！
Hey! Erina!
あっ！
エ… エリナ 待って！
E-Erina! Wait!
《何か変だぞ！
一体 何があったんだ？》
Something's wrong... what happened to her?
≪(少年たち)ヘヘヘ…｡
あっ！
Look here, boys! It's that loser, Jojo!
(少年１)
見ろよ ジョジョの情けねえ姿を！
(少年２)
おい 言ってやれよ｡ なぜ 彼女が
あんな態度をとるのかをよ｡
Someone ought to tell him why the poor lass was acting like that!
Oh, heavens no! I'd hate to see Jojo in tears again!
(少年１)やだよ｡ 俺 ジョジョが
悲しむ姿を 見たくねえもん｡
(少年たち)アッハハハ！
お… お前ら…｡
Y-You lot...
Erina...
エリナに…
エリナに 何をした～!?
What did you do to Erina?!
うお～っ！
DIO!
ディオ～‼
That's a name you should speak with a great deal more reverence!
人の名を！ 随分 気安く
呼んでくれるじゃあないか！
I'll never forgive you! You've been tormenting me since you got here!
決して許さない！ 君の
僕に対する 嫌がらせではない！
僕のことなど どうでもいい！
ほほう｡ さては 聞いたな｡
But I don't care what you do to me!
Well now, could it be that you've heard about your dear Erina?
あの 愛しの エリナのことを｡
そして 鉄拳による
報復に出ることを 考えたわけか｡
And now you plan to use those clenched fists to get your revenge?
I'll never forgive you for the way you disrespected her!
彼女に対する侮辱が 許せない！
There's nothing more pathetic than a man sick with jealousy!
見苦しいぞ！ 嫉妬に狂った姿は！
Do you really want to take another beating like you did in the ring, you imbecile?!
また ボクシングのように
されたいのか？ まぬけが！
I... I can't lay a hand on him...
《か… かなわない｡➡
If I lose now, I'll spend the rest of my life cowering in Dio's shadow...
でも ここで負けたら
これから 一生 ディオの陰で➡
おどおどと
生活しなくてはならない｡➡
But more importantly, I have to fight...
何よりも
エリナの名誉を 取り戻すため➡
戦わなくてはならない！》
I have to defend Erina's honor!
I'll take him down once and for all, and I'll do it fair and square!
《徹底的に
たたきのめしてやる！➡
それも 正々堂々とな｡➡
I will ensure that my superiority over Jojo is etched into his entire being!
そうすることによって➡
自分は もう この ディオには
勝てないということを➡
ジョジョ自身の体で
覚えるからだ｡➡
ケンカでも 人生でもな！》
Whether in battle... or life itself!
うぉぉ！
来い！
Come on!
うおおお！
Amazing! What a thrilling sensation!
いいぞ！ いい感触だ！
You... you're trying to grapple with me, even after that kick?!
こ… こいつ 蹴りを入れられて
つかんでくるとは｡
もう一撃 欲しいか！
I'll have to hit harder...
ゲッ！ うげぇぇぇぇっ！
ディオ～！
Dio!
This...
君が泣くまで 殴るのをやめない！
I'll keep beating you until I have you in tears!
This...
This piece of trash is laying his hands on me... Dio!
《こんな カスみたいなやつに
この ディオが！》
ぐわ～！
あっ…｡
よ… よくも｡
Y-You...
You... how dare you...
よくも よくも…｡
よくも！ この僕に向かって！
How dare you do this to me!
な… 涙…｡
H-He's crying?
この 汚らしい 阿呆が！
You filthy idiot!
You two! What's going on here?!
≪(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)
２人とも 一体 何事だ!?
Father!
父さん！
男子たるもの
ケンカの１つも するだろう｡
There is a time and a place for a gentleman to fight!
しかし ジョジョ！ 今のは
抵抗もできなくなった ディオを➡
But Jojo, from what I could see you were
attacking Dio while he was completely defenseless!
一方的に
殴っていたように見えた！➡
And that is not the way a gentleman behaves!
紳士のすることではない！
ち… 違う！
That's not-
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)言い訳 無用！
２人とも 部屋へ入っとれ！
No excuses! Both of you, go to your rooms!
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)
後で ２人とも 罰を与える！
I will decide your punishments later!
(庭師)ん？ あの箱 何じゃろ？
I wonder what that box is for...
Oh well, one of the maids must have thrown it away.
まあ いいか｡
メイドの誰かが 捨てたんじゃろ｡
(物音)
(庭師)ん？
(庭師)な… 何だ？
この ぶつかるような音は！
What... What the-?!
It sounds like something's hitting against the door!
ま… まさか
な… 中に誰かいるのだ‼
Oh no...
There's someone inside!
This is awful! They're being burned alive!
た… 大変だ！
生きたまま 焼かれているのだ！
エリナ…｡
Erina...
くそっ！ ディオ！
Damn you, Dio!
お前の くだらないキスは
これを 狙っていたのなら➡
If this is what you were after with that damn kiss, then congratulations!
予想以上の効果を上げたぞ！
His body was so badly burned...
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)あまりに
ひどい なきがらだったので➡
We took care of the burial to spare you the sight...
お前には見せずに 埋葬したよ｡➡
警察が言うには
恐らく 番犬が邪魔な➡
The police are saying it must have been a thief
that thought he was getting rid of a watchdog...
ぬすっとの
仕業だろうということだ｡
Dio...
ディオ…｡
(執事)ディオさん？
Master Dio? He hasn't returned from school yet.
まだ
学校から 帰っておりませんが｡
〈ジョジョは 自分の部屋へ行き
２時間 眠った〉
Jojo returned to his room and slept for two hours...
A while later, he awoke in his bed...
〈そして 目を覚ましてから
しばらくして➡
He remembered Danny's death... and cried.
ダニーが死んだことを 思い出し
泣いた〉
I dealt with that disgusting mutt as payback for my humiliation, but I didn't think Jojo would explode like that.
《バカ犬を始末し
屈辱は晴らしたが➡
あんな爆発力が
ジョジョにあるとは➡
見くびっていた｡➡
I underestimated him...
やつは たたけば たたくほど
成長するタイプだ｡➡
He's not the type to back down under pressure, he rises up against it.
自分の欠点は
怒りっぽいところだ｡➡
My pride is my greatest weakness... I'll have to reflect on this.
反省しなくては｡➡
もっと 自分の心を
冷静に コントロールするように➡
I need to learn how to better control my emotions!
成長しなくては！》
And thus, seven years passed...
〈そして ７年の歳月が経過する〉
♬(ｴﾝﾃﾞｨﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
♬ I'll be the roundabout
I'll be the roundabout
♬ The words
will make you out'n'out
The words will make you out 'n' out
♬ I spend the day away
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
♬～
♬ The music dance and sing
The music dance and sing
♬ They make
the children really ring
They make the children really ring
I'll spend the day your way
♬ Spend the day away
♬ Call it morning
driving through
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley
♬ In and around the lake
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
♬ Mountains come out of
the sky and they stand there
and they stand there
♬ One mile over we'll be there
and we'll see you
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
♬ Ten true summers
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
♬ we'll be there
and laughing too
♬ Twenty four before
my love you'll see
Twenty four before my love you'll see I'll be
♬ I'll be there with you
There with you
♬～
Next Episode
Seven years later...
Jonathan Joestar steals the ball!
I had a vision of something truly dreadful!
You don't mind losing your arm then, do you?
You'll lose that friendship!
I will protect my father, and the Joestar name!
Episode 2:
"Letter from the Past"
〈あれから ７年〉
(実況)ボールを 奪い取ったのは➡
ジョナサン･ジョースターだ！
僕は 今！➡
とても 恐ろしい想像をしている！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)指４本 失うぐらい
平気と言ったな！
友情を失うぞ！
僕は父を！
ジョースター家を守る！